<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kartini Teknologi</title><link>/en/</link><description>Recent content on Kartini Teknologi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 18 - Eraulia Nadinda Rachmat</title><link>/en/episodes/18/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/18/</guid><description>Guest Eraulia Nadinda Rachmat or Dinda is currently living in Hamburg, Germany and working as a software engineer at Mercury Media Technology GmbH. Before switching career to software engineering, she graduated with a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Business Management with Finance concentration from Bandung Institute of Technology.
Website Twitter LinkedIn Description In this episde, we talked with Eraulia Nadinda Rachmat or usually goes by Dinda. Dinda is currently working as a software engineer at Mercury Media Technology GmbH.</description></item><item><title>Transkrip - Episode 18 - Eraulia Nadinda Rachmat</title><link>/en/episodes/18/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/18/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi, episode 18. We now have a guest who comes from far away, from Hamburg, her name is Nadinda. She&amp;rsquo;s currently working as a Junior Software Engineer in Mercury Media Technology GmbH (how do you pronounce this, this is like a &amp;ldquo;PT&amp;rdquo; right in Germany?) how are you, Dinda?
Dinda (D): Good, despite of Corona, everything is well.
K: We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about a lot of things with Dinda, because she has a lot of experiences.</description></item><item><title>Episode 17 - Anbita Nadine Siregar</title><link>/en/episodes/17/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/17/</guid><description>Guest Anbita Nadine Siregar or Nadine is founder of Generation Girl. After graduating from Boston University with a degree in computer science, Nadine worked as a product engineer in Gojek for three years before being involved in Yayasan Generasi Maju Berkarya (YGMB)—the foundation that oversees programs such as Generation Girl and Pengajar Belajar—full-time. Besides of her work in YGMB, she is currently also pursuing a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in social entrepreneurship.</description></item><item><title>Transkrip - Episode 17 - Anbita Nadine Siregar</title><link>/en/episodes/17/transcript/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/17/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh here. Today we&amp;rsquo;re at episode 17 and we&amp;rsquo;re currently with Nadine Siregar, founder of Generation Girl, which is a program that some of you might have heard before. What is Generation Girl? We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about it with Nadine. But before that let&amp;rsquo;s say hi to her. Hi Nadine, how are you?
Nadine (N): Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m good, how are you?</description></item><item><title>Episode 16 - Aulia Rahmani</title><link>/en/episodes/16/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/16/</guid><description>Guest Aulia Rahmani is currently a Lead UI/UX Designer in Alterra. After finishing her studies in communication, she took up various roles from event organizer to front-end developer. She also writes about UX and design on her Medium and personal website.
Medium LinkedIn Twitter Personal website Description What is UX writing and what is the role of a UX writer? In this episode, we chat with Aulia Rahmani to discuss about UX writing - from what UX writers do, how do UX writers play a role in the development of a feature or product, the skills that you need to become a UX writer, to tools and techniques that UX writers often use in their day-to-day job.</description></item><item><title>Transkrip - Episode 16 - Aulia Rahmani</title><link>/en/episodes/16/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/16/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hello everyone, we are back again in Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh. We haven&amp;rsquo;t recorded for a long time, huh? The last time we recorded was like before fasting. So it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time. We&amp;rsquo;re very sorry. The reason is there really nothing specific. Perhaps because we have to adapt again because of the pandemic and everything else. Because even though I&amp;rsquo;m used to working remotely, this pandemic has changed everything.</description></item><item><title>Episode 15 - Farah Clara</title><link>/en/episodes/15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/15/</guid><description>Guest
Farah Clara is currently managing the Python Indonesia community and is also an AWS User Group Lead in Indonesia. Farah has been involved in many meetups and technology conferences in Indonesia such as PyCon Indonesia in 2018 and 2019.
Twitter LinkedIn Description If you&amp;rsquo;re involved in the tech communities in Indonesia, you may be familiar with the name Farah Clara or the username @sosispanggang. She most likely is also involved in the meetups or conferences that you have attended.</description></item><item><title>Transkrip - Episode 15 - Farah Clara</title><link>/en/episodes/15/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/15/transcript/</guid><description>** Kiki (K): ** Hello everyone! We return to Kartini Technology with Kiki and Galuh as usual. And, today we have a guest who you can say is the most requested guest anyway. I think I&amp;rsquo;ve heard people request her several times. So welcome Farah!
** Farah (F): ** Hello!
** K: ** [Laughter] How are you?
** F: ** Are there really many requests? [Laughter] Good.
** K: ** Good?</description></item><item><title>Episode 14 - Radita Liem</title><link>/en/episodes/14/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/14/</guid><description>Guest Radita Liem is a research assistant and PhD candidate at RWTH Aachen University. After graduated from her undergraduate study in UkDW Jogja, she worked at one of game companies from Japan and then at one unicorn companies in Indonesia before finally continued her master study in Estonia. Now she&amp;rsquo;s researching about High Performance Computing (HPC) for her doctorate study.
Instagram LinkedIn Description In this episode, we talked with Radita Liem, a research assistant and PhD candidate at RWTH Aachen University.</description></item><item><title>Transkrip - Episode 14 - Radita Liem</title><link>/en/episodes/14/transcript/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/14/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hello all! Welcome back to Kartini Teknologi,together with Kiki and Galuh here. We have Radita Liem with us today, she is a research assistant and PhD candidate also at the university RWTH Aachen University. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what the abbreviation stands for, so maybe we just ask directly to the Dita. Hello Dita!
Dita (D): Hello!
K: Are you now studying from home?
D: As a matter of fact, for my doctorate program, I&amp;rsquo;m already working on the research.</description></item><item><title>Episode 13 - Adzkia Salima</title><link>/en/episodes/13/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/13/</guid><description>Guest Adzkia Salima is a software engineer at Genetwister Technologies B.V. Adzkia is a computer science graduate from Institut Pertanian Bogor (IPB). Her child dream to be a doctor then took her to continue her master study at Wageningen University &amp;amp; Research majoring in bioinformatics.
Twitter Blog Description What happens when we combine computer science with biology? In this episode, we chat with Adzkia Salima, a software engineer with background in computer science in bioinformatics.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 13 - Adzkia Salima</title><link>/en/episodes/13/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/13/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone! In the midst of the corona outbreak, hopefully all is well. Anyway, we&amp;rsquo;re back again with Kiki and Galuh here. And as usual we will be chatting with one guest, this time the topic is interesting because we have never discussed it and it seems like a fairly new topic in Indonesia. It&amp;rsquo;s about bioinformatics. And with us now we have Adzkia Salima, she is a software engineer at Genetwister Technologies, right?</description></item><item><title>Episode 12 - Theresia Tanzil</title><link>/en/episodes/12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/12/</guid><description>Guest Theresia Tanzil is currently working as a Lead Solution Architect at a Data-as-a-Service company called Scrapinghub, where she gets to reverse engineer websites and systems on a daily basis, among other things. She also writes about various topics—from metacognition to information architecture—on her website, proses.id.
Twitter Website Description In this episode, we chatted with Theresia Tanzil who is currently working as a Lead Solution Architect at a Data-as-a-Service company called Scrapinghub.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 12 - Theresia Tanzil</title><link>/en/episodes/12/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/12/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh. Before we start chatting with our guest, we want to congratulate Galuh who has just become a Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning. Congrats!
Galuh (G): Thank you!
K: So cool. Anyway, talking about data, we have Theresia Tanzil with us. She&amp;rsquo;s a solution architect at ScrapingHub. Do you want to introduce yourself a little bit?
Tere (T): Sure.</description></item><item><title>Episode 11 - Adrianti Rusli</title><link>/en/episodes/11/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/11/</guid><description>Guest Adrianti Rusli is a front-end developer at JYSK Group, an R&amp;amp;D clinic &amp;amp; aesthetics companies that is based in Singapore. Besides of working in the front-end development field and dabbling in back-end development, she is also active in communities such as Perempuan WP and has spoken in various events and meetups such as Chrome Dev Summit Extended 2019 Jakarta.
Twitter LinkedIn Description In our first episode in 2020, we chatted with Adrianti Rusli who is currently working as a frontend developer at JYSK Group.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 11 - Adrianti Rusli</title><link>/en/episodes/11/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/11/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi. This is our eleventh episode I think, it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since we record a new episode, we&amp;rsquo;re very sorry! I think the tenth episode was even recorded in November or October, right Galuh?
Galuh (G): Yup.
K: Yeah. It&amp;rsquo;s been very hectic, and in January we focused on Global Diversity CFP Day, which we organized together. So we got kind of distracted, that&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re just getting back to Kartini Teknologi.</description></item><item><title>Episode 10 - Victoria Lestari</title><link>/en/episodes/10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/10/</guid><description>Guest Victoria Lestari is an alumni of University of Indonesia and University of Texas whose now is working as a Software Engineer at Google in London. Besides working at tech, she&amp;rsquo;s also an active writer in Quora and just recently published her novel, Jakarta Vigilante which talk about women superhero that took place in Jakarta.
Instagram Quora Description How is it like to work at Google? In this episode, we talked with Victoria Lestari, a Software Engineer at Google London.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 10 - Victoria Lestari</title><link>/en/episodes/10/transcript/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/10/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hello everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh as usual. And, today, we have another guest who is pretty active on Quora as well, and if you&amp;rsquo;re a Quora user maybe you know her already. Without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s welcome Victoria Lestari. Hello, Victoria.
Victoria (V): Hello, thank you so much Kiki and Galuh for inviting me to the podcast. This is the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been invited to a podcast, so I feel really honored, and a bit nervous, but hopefully everything will go well.</description></item><item><title>Episode 9 - Veni Johanna</title><link>/en/episodes/9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/9/</guid><description>Guest Veni Johanna is a Stanford alumni who now is working as an Engineering Manager in Quora. Apart from her role in Quora, she also co-founded a program called Indonesia Mengglobal whose mission is to increase Indonesian who study and excel globally. The program also provides mentorship for those want to study abroad.
Twitter LinkedIn Description What does an Engineer Manager do? In this episode, we talked with Veni Johanna, an Engineering Manager in Quora.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 9 - Veni Johanna</title><link>/en/episodes/9/transcript/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/9/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hello everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh. We have another special guest with us as always, and I think I&amp;rsquo;m personally excited for this guest, I just learned about her recently, but I think her profile perfectly portrays how a Kartini Teknologi should be. So yeah I&amp;rsquo;m super excited to have more conversation and chat more with her today. Right, Galuh?
Galuh (G): Yes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 8 - Velta Azizah Destiana</title><link>/en/episodes/8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/8/</guid><description>Guest Velta Azizah Destiana is an Interaction Designer at PigeonLine and User Experience (UX) Engineer at Toptal who is based in Dubai. Previously, she also has experiences as a Software Engineer and User Interface (UI) Architect. Velta graduated from University of Queensland with a degree in Computer Science and specialization in User Experience Design.
Twitter LinkedIn Description In this episode, we chatted with Velta Azizah Destiana, an Interaction Designer at PigeonLine and User Experience (UX) Engineer at Toptal.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 8 - Velta Azizah Destiana</title><link>/en/episodes/8/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/8/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to the Kartini Teknologi podcast with Galuh and Kiki here. I usually say Kiki first but now I&amp;rsquo;m mentioning Galuh first because today&amp;rsquo;s guest is Galuh&amp;rsquo;s request. But before we talk about that, I want to talk about how I&amp;rsquo;m so happy that we&amp;rsquo;re now at our eighth episode, and we haven&amp;rsquo;t run out of guests to invite yet. So, I want to say thanks to our previous guests and today&amp;rsquo;s guest for coming to Kartini Teknologi.</description></item><item><title>Episode 7 - Alanda Kariza</title><link>/en/episodes/7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/7/</guid><description>Guest Alanda Kariza is the Head of Community at Quora Indonesia. She graduated from University of Warwick with an MSc degree in behavioural economics. She also set up a social organization called Sinergi Muda which organizes the Indonesian Youth Conference. She has published 11 books, among them Beats Apart (2015) and Sophismata (2017).
Quora Twitter LinkedIn Description In this episode, Alanda Kariza shares about her role as a Head of Community at Quora in Indonesia, how her background in activism and behavioral sciences relate to her current role, and the impact of communities both in the tech industry and other industries as well.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 7 - Alanda Kariza</title><link>/en/episodes/7/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/7/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh here.
Galuh (G): Hello.
K: Currently there are three of us here with a special guest whose work I&amp;rsquo;ve been following for a while. I think this will be interesting because the topic will be a bit different from our previous episodes—previously we talked about data, machine learning&amp;hellip; and now we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss technology from another angle. So we want to let you know that in the tech industry you can also contribute in fields such as design or community, and now we&amp;rsquo;ll be talking about community.</description></item><item><title>Episode 6 - Zahra Amalia Syarifah</title><link>/en/episodes/6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/6/</guid><description>Guest Zahra Amalia Syarifah is a social sciences researcher and PhD student in sociology in UC San Diego. Zahra&amp;rsquo;s research interest focuses on religious politics, political network, social movement organization, political participation, and democratization. Zahra also uses computational techniques in the various researches that she is conducting, such as natural language processing and network analysis.
Twitter LinkedIn Description We chatted with Zahra Amalia Syarifah, a social sciences researcher and PhD student in sociology in UC San Diego, about how she utilizes computational techniques for her researches in the field of social sciences.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 6 - Zahra Amalia Syarifah</title><link>/en/episodes/6/transcript/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/6/transcript/</guid><description>K (Kiki): Hi everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh here. Today, we have a really exciting guest with us, and just like the previous episode we&amp;rsquo;re recording live so we&amp;rsquo;re sorry if you can hear some noises. Hopefully everything will be going well. Well anyway, Galuh, do you want to introduce us to our guest? Galuh is the one that suggests her to be our next guest.</description></item><item><title>Episode 5 - Vanya Valindria</title><link>/en/episodes/5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/5/</guid><description>Guest Vanya Valindria is a machine learning researcher and research scientist based in London. Vanya also has a PhD degree from Imperial College London. Besides having extensive experiences in the field of machine learning, especially medical image analysis, Vanya is also passionate in tech and music.
Website LinkedIn BandCamp YouTube Article about Vanya Valindria in Women of Indonesia Career Network Description Vanya Valindria is a machine learning researcher and research scientist based in London.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 5 - Vanya Valindria</title><link>/en/episodes/5/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/5/transcript/</guid><description>K (Kiki): Hi everyone, we&amp;rsquo;re back at Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh here.
G (Galuh): Hello.
K: This is our first time recording onsite, usually we record using video conference, but now we have a special guest and we happen to be able to do this recording together&amp;hellip; so there are three of us here, and our guest is Vanya.
V (Vanya): Okay, I&amp;rsquo;m Vanya, and I currently work as a machine learning researcher as well as a research scientist.</description></item><item><title>Episode 4 - Desy Kristianti</title><link>/en/episodes/4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/4/</guid><description>Guest Desy Kristianti is a technology consultant in Deloitte who specializes in Enterprise Integrations. She is also active as a public speaker, co-founder of Women of Indonesia Career Network, and organizer of a public speaking group called The SPUDS in Belfast. She enjoys meeting new people, attending talks, watching musicals or learning music.
Website LinkedIn Description What does a technology consultant do? In this episode, we chatted with Desy Kristianti, a technology consultant who works in Deloitte Belfast, Northern Ireland.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 4 - Desy Kristianti</title><link>/en/episodes/4/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/4/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since our last episode. Galuh and I haven&amp;rsquo;t recorded a new episode in two month, we&amp;rsquo;re so sorry. Last month there was a long holiday for the Eid, and after the Eid I had a work week, and Galuh was away too. So it was really hectic. We&amp;rsquo;ve just got the chance to record a new episode now. But don&amp;rsquo;t worry, because now our guest is just as awesome as our previous guests.</description></item><item><title>Episode 3 - Retno Ika</title><link>/en/episodes/3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/3/</guid><description>Guest Retno Ika Safitri ia a tech-enterpreneur, co-founder of Tanibox and Product Strategist at Chloe &amp;amp; Matt. Through Tanibox, she launched a farm management system, Tania.
Instagram
Description Have you ever dreamed to run a business overseas? In this episode, we talked about technology from the business perspective with Retno Ika (@retnoika.s), Co-founder of Tanibox, an Estonian-based startup that focus on sustainable agriculture. This is the longest episode so far!</description></item><item><title>Transkrip - Episode 3 - Retno Ika</title><link>/en/episodes/3/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/3/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to the Kartini Teknologi podcast with Kiki and Galuh. We&amp;rsquo;re now at episode three, time flies so fast&amp;hellip; and today, we have a special guest who is no less special than our previous guests. In our previous episodes we talked about technology from the perspective of education and then social. Now we&amp;rsquo;ll talk more about the business side. We&amp;rsquo;re now with Retno Ika Safitri, or usually called Ocha.</description></item><item><title>Episode 2 - Asanilta Fahda</title><link>/en/episodes/2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/2/</guid><description>Guest Asanilta Fahda is the initiator and is a part of the team behind PilahPilihPilpres.com&amp;mdash;a website that helps voters to determine their pick for the 2019 Indonesian presidential election based on the candidates&amp;rsquo; programs and ideas. Aside of that, she also worked as a software engineer in Shopee Singapore as a part of the Natural Language Processing (NLP) team. Besides of technology, she also has interests in the arts and social issues.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 2 - Asanilta Fahda</title><link>/en/episodes/2/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/2/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh.
Galuh (G): Hello!
K: Today we&amp;rsquo;ll be talking about something that we have just done&amp;hellip; probably around three weeks ago&amp;hellip; the presidential election! Or actually the general elections, but we&amp;rsquo;ll specifically talk about the presidential election. Anyway. About this presidential election, we already have one special guest, Asanilta Fahda.
G: So Asanilta is a graduate of ITB. She&amp;rsquo;s a former software engineer in Shopee Singapore in the Natural Language Processing team, and she&amp;rsquo;s also the initiator and coordinator of a website that&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Episode 1 - Amy Wibowo</title><link>/en/episodes/1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/1/</guid><description>Guest Amy Wibowo is a programmer and alumni of MIT, Honda, University of Tokyo Igarashi Lab, and Airbnb who is now focusing on redefining computer science education through her business, BubbleSort Zines.
Twitter
Description Amy shares her thoughts on computer science education, how she builds her business, the wearable Clipper Card ring that she created that Bay Area talks about, also how she can accomplish all those while staying true to herself.</description></item><item><title>Transcript - Episode 1 - Amy Wibowo</title><link>/en/episodes/1/transcript/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/1/transcript/</guid><description>Kiki (K): Hi welcome back to the Kartini Teknologi podcast.
Galuh (G): Hi! Welcome back to our show.
K: So this is our very first episode with a guest and we have a very special guest with us today, Amy Wibowo. Hi Amy, how are you doing?
Amy (A): Hi, thank you so much for having me.
G: Thank you so much for coming on our show. We&amp;rsquo;re both huge fans of your work so we&amp;rsquo;re so excited to have you here.</description></item><item><title>Credit and tools</title><link>/en/credits-and-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/credits-and-tools/</guid><description> There are tons of other creative folk&amp;rsquo;s work and tools that we use to make this podcast happen.
Credits Icon used for our logo made by mynamepong from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY Bumper music is Free horses by Stefan Kartenberg. Licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution Noncommercial (3.0) license. Ibu Kita Kartini song in the 1st episode is by Fathur I Tools Notion as project management tool Canva for visual editing Hugo as our website platform Audacity for audio editing Zoom as video conference recording tool</description></item><item><title>Episode 0 - Introduction</title><link>/en/episodes/0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/episodes/0/</guid><description>Hey all! Counting days to the Kartini&amp;rsquo;s day, when we will launch our Podcast, Kartini Teknologi, we want to introduce ourselves as the hosts. Also to tell you about why we create this podcast in the first place. Plus, to give you a sneak peek about our very first guest next week.
Nice to meet you and see you all in the next episode!
-- Segments 1:26 - Kiki&amp;rsquo;s introduction</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/about/</guid><description>Indonesia needs more women in the technology industry. Technology has come to dominate people&amp;rsquo;s lives. When the creators of technology is dominated by certain groups, there will be bias which will cause disparity in the resulting products.
We believe in the virtues of diversity. Through Kartini Teknologi, we want to encourage more Indonesian women to get involved in the technology industry. The objective is to reduce or even close the tech industry&amp;rsquo;s gender gap.</description></item><item><title>Guest Notes</title><link>/en/guest-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/guest-notes/</guid><description>Hi! Before we get started, we&amp;rsquo;d like to say thank you for being with us here at Kartini Teknologi. In this page, you can find a few things that might be helpful for you before our conversation. 🙌
We can do our conversation in two ways: face-to-face &amp;amp; remote conversation. These notes are primarily aimed at guests who we&amp;rsquo;ll be having remote conversations with.
What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need Being able to hear each other clearly is essential in the making of a good conversation.</description></item></channel></rss>