<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kartini Teknologi</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kartini Teknologi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3 - Retno Ika</title>
      <link>/en/episodes/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/episodes/3/</guid>
      <description>Guest Retno Ika Safitri ia a tech-enterpreneur, co-founder Tanibox and Product Strategist Cloe &amp;amp; Matt. Through Tanibox, she launched a farm management system, Tanibox.
Instagram
Description Have you ever dream to run a business overseas? In this episode, we talked about technology from the business perspective with Retno Ika (@retnoika.s), Co-founder of Tanibox, an Estonian-based startup that focus on sustainable agriculture. This is the longest episode so far! You have to listen if you ever dreamed about running a business, especially in tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transkrip - Episode 3 - Retno Ika</title>
      <link>/en/episodes/3/transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/episodes/3/transcript/</guid>
      <description>TBD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2 - Asanilta Fahda</title>
      <link>/en/episodes/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/episodes/2/</guid>
      <description>Guest Asanilta Fahda is the initiator and is a part of the team behind PilahPilihPilpres.com&amp;mdash;a website that helps voters to determine their pick for the 2019 Indonesian presidential election based on the candidates&amp;rsquo; programs and ideas. Aside of that, she also worked as a software engineer in Shopee Singapore as a part of the Natural Language Processing (NLP) team. Besides of technology, she also has interests in the arts and social issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcript - Episode 2 - Asanilta Fahda</title>
      <link>/en/episodes/2/transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/episodes/2/transcript/</guid>
      <description>Kiki (K): Hi everyone, welcome back to Kartini Teknologi with Kiki and Galuh.
Galuh (G): Hello!
K: Today we&amp;rsquo;ll be talking about something that we have just done&amp;hellip; probably around three weeks ago&amp;hellip; the presidential election! Or actually the general elections, but we&amp;rsquo;ll specifically talk about the presidential election. Anyway. About this presidential election, we already have one special guest, Asanilta Fahda.
G: So Asanilta is a graduate of ITB. She&amp;rsquo;s a former software engineer in Shopee Singapore in the Natural Language Processing team, and she&amp;rsquo;s also the initiator and coordinator of a website that&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1 - Amy Wibowo</title>
      <link>/en/episodes/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/episodes/1/</guid>
      <description>Guest Amy Wibowo is a programmer and alumni of MIT, Honda, University of Tokyo Igarashi Lab, and Airbnb who is now focusing on redefining computer science education through her business, BubbleSort Zines.
Twitter
Description Amy shares her thoughts on computer science education, how she builds her business, the wearable Clipper Card ring that she created that Bay Area talks about, also how she can accomplish all those while staying true to herself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcript - Episode 1 - Amy Wibowo</title>
      <link>/en/episodes/1/transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/episodes/1/transcript/</guid>
      <description>Kiki (K): Hi welcome back to the Kartini Teknologi podcast.
Galuh (G): Hi! Welcome back to our show.
K: So this is our very first episode with a guest and we have a very special guest with us today, Amy Wibowo. Hi Amy, how are you doing?
Amy (A): Hi, thank you so much for having me.
G: Thank you so much for coming on our show. We&amp;rsquo;re both huge fans of your work so we&amp;rsquo;re so excited to have you here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit and tools</title>
      <link>/en/credits-and-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/credits-and-tools/</guid>
      <description> There are tons of other creative folk&amp;rsquo;s work and tools that we use to make this podcast happen.
Credits  Icon used for our logo made by mynamepong from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY Bumper music is Free horses by Stefan Kartenberg. Licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution Noncommercial (3.0) license. Ibu Kita Kartini song in the 1st episode is by Fathur I  Tools  Notion as project management tool Canva for visual editing Hugo as our website platform Audacity for audio editing Zoom as video conference recording tool  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 0 - Introduction</title>
      <link>/en/episodes/0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/episodes/0/</guid>
      <description>Hey all! Counting days to the Kartini&amp;rsquo;s day, when we will launch our Podcast, Kartini Teknologi, we want to introduce ourselves as the hosts. Also to tell you about why we create this podcast in the first place. Plus, to give you a sneak peek about our very first guest next week.
Nice to meet you and see you all in the next episode!
 Segments 1:26 - Kiki&amp;rsquo;s introduction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Indonesia needs more women in the technology industry. Technology has come to dominate people&amp;rsquo;s lives. When the creators of technology is dominated by certain groups, there will be bias which will cause disparity in the resulting products.
We believe in the virtues of diversity. Through Kartini Teknologi, we want to encourage more Indonesian women to get involved in the technology industry. The objective is to reduce or even close the tech industry&amp;rsquo;s gender gap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Notes</title>
      <link>/en/guest-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/guest-notes/</guid>
      <description>Hi! Before we get started, we&amp;rsquo;d like to say thank you for being with us here at Kartini Teknologi. In this page, you can find a few things that might be helpful for you before our conversation. 🙌
We can do our conversation in two ways: face-to-face &amp;amp; remote conversation. These notes are primarily aimed at guests who we&amp;rsquo;ll be having remote conversations with.
What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need Being able to hear each other clearly is essential in the making of a good conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>